（犬の遠吠え）
（アランドロン）
＜むかしむかし　ある所に→
Once upon a time, in a land far far away,
それはそれは　凶悪で
残忍で傍若無人で→
there was a barbaric, ruthless, and defiant,
人を人とも思わぬ
悪魔のような男がおりました＞
demon-like bastard who thought
nothing of his fellow man.
（ベル坊）ビエエエ～ン！
（男鹿）ぎゃあああ～！くっそ～！
Shit!
こんな夜中に　ぐずりやがって！
Why are you so cranky in
the middle of the night?!
ダウー！
一体　何だってんだよ！ダ～イヤ！
What the hell do you want?
仕方ねぇ　これか？
（ガランガラン）
Fine, here you go.
やっぱうるせえ。そうか！
Damn that noise is annoying!
Ah! If he wants a loud noise,
then how 'bout a pair of these?
デケエ音でいいなら
これでもいけるんじゃね～か？
アイ！？
♪～（ヘッドフォン）
ア～！
ヘビメタ…みたいな。
Heavy Metal! Or something like it...
じゃあ　もう少し
音量を上げてっと。
Then I'll just raise the volume a little...
アイー！
おっ！しめしめ～。
じゃあ　今のうちに俺も。
Got this in the bag... Now
while I have the chance...
♪～（大音量）
ヒィッ！！
（美咲）今　何時だと思ってんの～！？
Do you have any idea what time it is?!
いやっ　べ　ベル坊が…。
Yeah! But! Baby Beel was...
近所迷惑でしょう！
（バタン！）
You'll wake up the neighbors!
ン～ブ　ビエエエエーッ！
ぎゃああああ～！
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語。
ただし　その赤ん坊は→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
普通の赤ん坊ではなく
魔王の子だったのです！＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
There is Nothing that Money Can't Buy
（下川）うん？
（阿部）あ～？
お　おが～何オメー
こっち見てんだよっ！
Oga... What're you starin' at me for, huh?
いや　見てね～のか
ど　どっちだ　コラッ！
Wait, you're not looking...
W-Which is it, huh?
でめぇ　神崎さん　倒したからって
いい気になってんじゃね～ぞ！
Look here, buddy... Don't go thinkin' you're
hot stuff just 'cause you beat Kanzaki-san!
すぴ～すぴ～。
ん？
え？
すぴ～すぴ～。
あ？
すぴ～。
あ～立ったまま寝とる！
He's asleep while standing!
下川　コイツはチャンスだ！
Shimokawa! This is our chance!
おう！ホントに
グッナ～イさせてやるぜ～！！
Yeah! I'm gonna make him say
good-night, once and for all!
ぐあああ～！！
ひゃはあ～！
寝不足パーンチ！
Sleep-deprived Punch!
（阿部）はあ～！
（下川）ええ～！？
（ドドゴッ！）
ダーブー！
…たく何が　ダーブーだよ。
オメーのせいで寝不足だぜ。
What the hell does "Da-bu-!" even mean?
It's your damn fault I'm sleepy.
な　なんて地獄絵図。
つ～か　やられんの　はやっ！
H-He's like some hellspawn...
And damn, they lost fast.
（古市）もぐもぐ…あ～ん。
ぐっ　うわっちっちぃっ～！
あ～オレのコロッケパン！
ああっ！
くちゃくちゃくちゃ　ごっくん。
My croquet sandwich!
*Munchymunchyswallow*
はっ　どこだここは？
いけね～寝ぼけちまった。
W-Where am I?
Crap, I must have dozed off!
ウソつけ～！
あ？
You big liar!
何だこりゃ？
ベル坊の落書きか？
What's this?
Did Baby Beel scribble on it?
（ヒルダ）ほぉ～これはアレだな。
Oh, that must be... Yes, it's that.
（アランドロン）ほほぉ～これは
見事なまでにアレですな。
Quite a fine specimen of that.
ヒルダさん！？
テメーら　どっから
わいてきやがったぁ！？
Hilda-san!
Where the hell did you come from?
騒ぐな。坊っちゃまに
ミルクを届けに来ただけだ。
Don't get excited. I simply came
to deliver milk for my master.
つ～か　アレって何だ！？アレって。
And what the hell is it?
このキモイのは何だ！？
This thing is creepin'
me out, whatever it is!
ご説明しましょう。
これは　ゼブルスペル。
Let me explain!
That is the Zebul Spell.
簡単に言えば
坊っちゃまとの契約の印です。
To put is simply, it's a symbol of
your contract with the young master.
契約？
ダーブ。
Contract?
光栄に思え！過去　数千年→
Think of it as an honor!
Over the past few millennia,
魔王に認められた人間など
数える程しかいない！
there have only been a handful of humans
who have been recognized by a Demon Lord.
全然　うれしかね～よ！
ブーイ。
That doesn't make me feel better at all.
（古市）
あ　あの～ちょっといいですか？
ん？
U-Um...
Can I ask a question?
今更っすけど
何で魔王に親が必要なんですか？
Sorry if this is a bit late... But why
does the Demon Lord need a parent anyway?
人間を滅ぼすだけなら
親なんていらないんじゃ…。
You don't need parents to
destroy humanity, so...
そうだぜ！
親というのは　言わば→
Yeah, what he said!
The "parent" is basically a vessel which
enables the Demon Lord to use his powers.
魔王が力を使う為の
入れ物なんですよ。
入れ物？
Vessel?
ダー！
何だ今度は！腹が減ったのか？
What is it now? You hungry?
（アランドロン）
魔王の力は
入れ物の大きさに左右されます。
The power of the Demon Lord is
influenced by the size of the vessel.
つまり　より強い力を出すには
相応の入れ物が必要になる訳です。
In other words, to use great power
requires a similarly matched vessel.
その強さを示すのが
ゼブルスペルってやつなのか？
And this Zebul Spell mark
shows how strong you are?
イエス！さすが知将　古市さま。
Yes! Lord Strategist Furuichi, I applaud you!
これでど～だ？
ダーブ。
How about this?
ど～よ　オレ。
How do you like me now?
Then, as congratulations for being
correct, I'll give you a big, warm...
では　正解のご褒美に
私の熱～い抱擁を！
いらね～よ！
あ　そうですか…。
I don't need that from you!
Oh, I see how it is...
何だよ！何が
気に食わないんだ　お前！
What?
What's got your goat, man?
その印は
坊っちゃまに懐かれるほどに→
The mark will grow along with
the master's attachment to you.
大きく複雑に成長します。
つまり…。
In other words...
貴様が　ボロクソに相手を殴れば
殴るほど　その力は強まり…。
The power will grow the more you
beat the crap out of your opponents.
真の魔王へ　近付くという訳だ！
Coming ever closer to the
true power of a Demon Lord!
((ギャーオ))
((ヘッヘッヘッ…))
好き勝手　言ってんじゃねえっ！
Don't say it like it's a good thing!
つ～か　どうすりゃ
なおるんだよ　これ！
I wanna know how to get rid of it!
いや～だから
殴らなきゃいいんだろ。
Then... Just don't punch anybody?
ん！？おお！
わかった。オレはもう
ケンカはしない。
Understood. No more fighting for me.
は？
Listen, Furuichi.
いいか古市　人を殴らなけりゃ
この印は　どんどん小さくなって→
As long as I stop hitting people this
mark will get smaller and smaller.
無くなっちまう。
そうすりゃ　ベル坊との契約も→
Then, my contract with
Baby Beel will be broken.
ナシってことになるんだよ。
よし　決めた！
I've made up my mind!
人は殴らねえ！
土下座もさせねえ！
I won't punch people! I won't
make them grovel before me!
オレは　スーパーいい人と
呼ばれるようになってやる！
Thus I will be what people
call a super nice guy!
いや　それは普通の人だ。
Uh, no. You'd be, like, a normal person.
うっせえ～！
（古市）ぐっへえ～っ！
Shut up!
おお！宣言した矢先の
約束破り。お見事！！
You broke the promise you
just made! Excellent!
ぐおおっ～しまったぁ～！
Aw, crap!
やはり　こんな男に坊っちゃまを
委ねたのは　間違いだったか…。
I knew it... Maybe it was a mistake
to entrust the master to this man.
（不良）姫川さん　頼まれてた
男鹿の嫁の写真っす！
Himekawa-san... These are the pictures
of Oga's wife you asked for.
（姫川）いいねぇ～ご苦労。
こいつは報酬だ。取っときな。
Nice. Good work. Here's your reward.
Take it and go.
（不良）へえ～こんなに！
This much?
All right! Time for a yogurti splurge!
（女子）新しい子？
わ～ゴスロリだぁ！
A new girl?
Ooh, a gothic lolita!
っていうか　おっぱいでか～！
あはは…牛かっての。
And her boobs are huge!
You wanna pet cow?
（姫川）
あのさ　もう少し
頭のいい会話してくんない？
Please, can you provide some
more intelligent conversation?
品のない女って嫌いなんだよね。
I hate unsophisticated women...
や～ん　こわ～い。
でも　そこにしびれる。
Ooh, scary!
But that's what makes you so exciting!
（鈴木）
じゃあよ　品のない男は好きか？→
So you like unsophisticated men, huh?
ひっひっひ…まさか自分が
襲われると思わなかったか？
Never thought you'd be attacked, did ya?
（女子）ははっ…。
フン。
あ？
いくらだ？
い？
How much?
いくら出しゃあ　オレの下に
付くかって聞いてんだよ？
I asked how much for me to buy your services?
（鈴木）は？何だそりゃ。
命乞いのつもりか？
What? Begging for your life?
ちゃんと状況みてしゃべれや！
Take a look at the situation you're in, huh?
うんうん　だからね…。
Yes, I have already...
状況的には
あとお前だけなんだわ。
And the situation I see
is you're the odd man out.
え？
≪ヘッヘッヘッ…≫
（ピーヒョロロ…）
（鈴木）ひっ！
策を弄するなら完璧に…だ。
If you're going to come up with
a plan, make sure it's perfect.
１度だけ　チャンスをやる。
明日までにこの女を連れて来い。→
I'll give you one chance.
Tomorrow, bring this woman to me.
いいな！
うんうん。
Got it?
（真田弟）兄者　聞いたか？姫川が
本格的に動くらしいぞ。
Bro, did you hear?
Himekawa is starting somethin' for real!
（真田兄）
奴（やつ）は狡猾（こうかつ）な男だからな。
さすがの男鹿もおしまいか。
That guy's one crafty bastard...
It's over, even for Oga!
へっへっ…ぜって～死んだな。
くははは…。
He's dead-meat for sure!
お　男鹿っ！？
や　やろうって～のか？
Oga?!
Y-You gonna...
オレ　暴力とか　嫌いっすから。
I... am against violence!
（真田兄弟）ええ～っ！？
ブー　ギー。
ふぁ～。
おほほ…。
（城山）神崎さんの見舞い？
Coming to visit Kanzaki-san?
（夏目）
そうそう　ヨーグルッチ持って
押しかけたら　きっと喜ぶよ！
Yes, exactly. I've brought yogurti,
so I'm sure he'll be pleased.
フン。そうか？
オレは嫌がると思うが…。
Oh? I think he'll be ticked off.
そんなことねぇ～って。
Don't say that...
ほら　神崎君って
ああ見えて　ツンデレ。
Kanzaki-kun might not look it,
but he's one of those tsundere...
（阿部）≪しかし　あの男鹿が
逃げるとは…≫
But I can't believe Oga ran away!
（下川）やっぱ姫川が原因だろ。
It must be Himekawa's doing.
（阿部）
アバレオーガも人の子か？→
Even the rampaging ogre has his match!
じゃあ　神崎倒したのも
案外マグレかもな。
Hmm, maybe him beating
Kanzaki was mostly a fluke?
や～れやれ。みんな
浮き足立ってるねえ。
Sheesh... Everyone's a bit fidgety lately.
石矢魔　東邦神姫。
The Ishiyama TKKH.
その一角をなしてた
神崎君もやられちゃったから→
I suppose it's only natural with one
of its corners, Kanzaki-kun, defeated.
それも仕方ないかもね。
オレたちも　そろそろ…。
We should also get to...
夏目…。
ん？
Natsume...
去りたければ去れ。オレは残る。
If you want to run, do
it. But I'm staying here.
いいかベル坊。男ってのは一度決め
たことは貫き通さなきゃならねぇ。
Listen up, Baby Beel. When a man makes
up his mind, he never ever changes it!
わかるな！
ダ！
You understand?
オレはもう　ケンカをしねえ！
そう自分で決めた。
I will no longer fight!
That is what I've decided.
アイ？
だから　お前も約束しろ！
もしもオレがそれを守れたら→
So, you promise as well!
If I keep that promise, you are not
going to cry then, no matter what!
そん時は　絶対に泣かねえってな！
男と男の約束だ！できるか！？
It's a promise, man-to-man. Will you promise?
ダ！
（アランドロン）よろしかったのですか？
ん？
Are you okay with this?
（アランドロン）ゼブルスペルのこと
教えてしまって。
I ended up telling him about the Zebul Spell.
構わん。それで奴が坊っちゃまから
離れるなら好都合だ。
I do not care.
If he uses it to distance himself from
the master, that would please me greatly.
またそんな言い方を…。本当は
期待しているんじゃないですか？
There you go again...
Aren't you actually expecting
good things from him?
フン　どうかな。いずれにせよ
このまま終われば→
I wonder...
If that's how he ends it, we'll know
that he wasn't anything special.
その程度の男だったというだけだ。
お？
（不良達）いたぞ～男鹿だぁ～！
There he is! It's Oga! Oga!
（不良達）お～待てコラー！
オレは男の約束を守るんだ～！
I'm going to keep my man's promise!
お　あきらめたか。
Did he give up?
どうした男鹿。
今日は逃げの一手か！？
What's the matter, Oga? Is
running all you can do today?
もう逃げらんね～ぜ！
フッ。
You can't run any more.
アイ。
（不良達）あっ！！
（ドッボーン）
はっはっは…アホどもが。ついて
これるもんなら　ついてこい！
Idiots!
You want me, then come and get me!
（古市）いや～しかし偶然ですね。
こんな所で出会うなんて。
But what a coincidence meeting here!
それはどうでもいいが
何故ついてくる？
I really don't care.
Why are you following me?
やだなぁ～ヒルダさん。
帰り道が一緒なだけですよ。
Now, now, Hilda-san... It's just that
our homes are in the same direction.
あれは？
え？
That's...
Hey, Oga's wife.
（鈴木）よ～男鹿の嫁。
Ooh, wow... Just as Himekawa-san predicted.
すげ～ぜ。
姫川さんのヨミ通りだな。
姫川って　確か東邦神姫の…。
Himekawa? The one from the TKKH?
《ほう…》
つ～わけで　拉致られてもらうぜ！！
So now you're gonna be our hostages!
（不良達）うわぁ～！！
（古市）え～っ！？ちょ…！
Whoa!
いって～な。…ってどこだ　ここ？
Ow...
Where am I?
あ？ひっ！ヒルダさん！？
H-Hilda-san?
Why has Hilda-san...
どうして　ヒルダさんが？
You've got to be kidding me!
ウソだろ！？
（鈴木）目が覚めたか？→
Eyes open?
女なら　当分起きねえぜ。
The girl ain't wakin' up.
What have you done?
（古市）何をした！？
（鈴木）何をした？→
What have we done? You don't get
the position you're in, do you?
立場が分かってねえようだな。
That's what you get for underestimating us!
あまりナメた口きいてっと→
I'll melt those lips right off!
その口　溶けちまうぜ！
うわぁ！
Don't go doing anything stupid.
余計なことしてんじゃねえよ。
ひ　姫川さん！
Himekawa-san?!
Himekawa? So he's the mastermind?
《姫川…こいつが主犯》
I see. This is quite the catch.
なるほど　こりゃあ上玉だ。
で　コイツは？
And this guy?
He's one of Oga's followers! We
brought him together with the woman.
（鈴木）男鹿の連れっす。女と一緒に
いたんで　連れてきました。
うん？
エッ！？
うわぁ！ああぁ～…。
（姫川）オレの完璧な計画が狂ったら
どうしてくれるんだ　コラ！
What the hell do you think you're
doing, messing with my perfect plan?
S-orry!
（鈴木）すい　すいません。
（姫川）
すいませんじゃ　ねえんだよ！→
Sorry ain't gonna cut it!
You worthless trash!
ったく　使えねえな！
（ドカッ！ドカッ！）
Well, this guy has some good
points to him after all.
ハッ！
中々見所のある奴ではないか。
Hilda-san, you're awake?
ヒルダさん！
気がついたんですか？
Yes. But it seems I have been drugged.
ああ　だが何か薬を
かがされたらしい。
I can't move properly.
体の自由がきかん。
ひええ～！
Now then...
さてと　おめざめになってんなら
男鹿君を呼び出してぇんだ。→
If you're awake, it's time
to call Oga-kun here.
Will you let me borrow your cell phone?
携帯かしてもらおうか。
Cell phone? What's that?
携帯？何だ　それは？
そんな物　持っておらんぞ。
I don't have anything like that.
そうかい。
I see.
Stop it!
やめろ！
サービス　サービス！
Service, service!
おおっ！楽し～な　これ。
This is fun!
But, I told you to cut it out!
やめろって言ってんだろ！
Hold it! Stay calm there.
（不良）
おおっと　大人しくしろ！
ひひひ…。う～ん　困った。→
Dang. It looks like you really
don't have a cell phone.
本当に携帯　持ってなさそうだな。
If you need a cell phone,
then why not use mine?
携帯なら
オレのを使えばいいだろ！
…だよね～。
Yes...
What trash...
ゲスが…。
ブゥ～。
はぁはぁ…いいか　ベル坊
男の約束ってのはな…あ？
Listen, Baby Beel... You
can't break a man's promise!
Shimokawa, this is our chance!
下川　こいつもチャンスだ。→
Oga, you bastard! How dare you
win fights and then run away!
男鹿　コノヤロ！
てめぇ　勝ち逃げは許さねぇ！
Oga! It's finally gonna be
a great good-night for you!
男鹿～　今度こそ
グレート　グッナイさせてやるぜ！
Out of the frying pan and into the fire...
何で　次から次へと。
（携帯の着信音）
おっ　もしも～し！
Hello?
き　き　きけぇ～！
男鹿～！
Oga!
Shut up! I can't hear!
うるせ～！！
聞こえんだろうがぁ！
Uh... hello?
あ～　もしもし？
[TEL]（姫川）もしもし　男鹿君？
Hello, Oga-kun?
誰だ　てめぇ。
Who the hell are you?
You're not Furuichi.
[TEL]古市じゃねえな。
（姫川）あ　いいよ
そういうリアクションは。→
Now don't react like that...
I'm making demands here, so listen!
用件だけ言うから　聞いてろ。→
君の嫁と友達は預かりました。
返してほしけりゃ→
We have your wife and your friend.
We'd like to return them to you,
but we need you to come here alone.
今から言うとこまで１人で来い。
I-It's over?
お　終わった？
Oga's takin' his time.
≪男鹿の奴　おっせ～な≫
フフッ…　バーカ！
あいつが来るわけねえだろう。
Idiots. He isn't coming.
He swore not to fight anymore!
もうケンカしねえっつってたよ
そういやぁ。ウッ！
Furuichi...
古市！
せいぜい祈るんだな。→
I suggest you pray hard. Because if he
doesn't show up, you ain't leavin' here unharmed.
奴が来なきゃ　てめえら
たたじゃ帰れねぇんだからな。
来ますよ。あいつは　絶対来る。
そういう奴です。
He'll come. Definitely.
That's the kind of guy he is.
Himekawa-san... Someone is
here. Someone is coming!
姫川さん！人影です！
誰か入ってきました！
Okay. Everyone, hide!
（姫川）よ～し　とりあえず囲め。
See?
ほらね。
（ドカッ！バキッ！）
ああ？
ヒ～ヒ～フ～…。
（不良）何だ　このオッサン？
What's with this big dude?
Actually, he was pretty weak.
（不良）異様に弱かったな。
フフッ　残念だが
タイムリミットだ。
Sorry, but the time limit is up.
うう…男鹿のアホー！
ボケ！カスー！
Oga, you idiot! You dolt!
You pea-brained prick!
Who're you callin' an idiot, huh?
≪誰がアホだ！コラッ！≫
ん！？
うん？
（アランドロン）ヒ～ヒ～フ～→
ヒ～ヒ～フ～…ヒ～ヒ～フ～！
エッ！？
You bastards...
ったく　てめぇら！
世話やかしてんじゃ　ねえぞ！
Goin' and getting yourselves kidnapped?!
（不良達）うおおっ！
Oga Punch! Punch! Punch! Punch!
男鹿パンチ　パンチ　パ～ンチ！
（不良達）ぐはははぁ～！
（ドサッ　ドサッ…）
Weren't you not fighting any more?
ケンカしねぇんじゃ
なかったのかよ。
What I'm doing now is...
ケンカじゃねぇよ。
今からすんのは。
ブゥ～…。
王の…→
...the Lord's justice!
処刑だ！
How much?
いくらだ？
あ？
お前　いくらでオレの下につく？
How much to make you my follower?
Not a bad deal, I say. I'll prepare
whatever reward you desire.
悪い話じゃねぇぜ。
望む報酬を用意しよう。→
オレとお前が組みゃ　石矢魔統一
なんて　わけねぇんだからな。
With the two of us combined, running
Ishiyama should be a cinch...
But, in the first place...
つ～か…誰だ　てめぇ？
...who are you?
（不良達）えええ～！？
Hey, don't play dumb!
オラァ！すらっとぼけてんじゃねぇぞ！ダボが！
There's no way you've never heard of
Himekawa-san if you go to Ishiyama!
石矢魔住んでて
姫川さん　知らねぇわけねぇだろ！
He's one of the TKKH! The TKKH!
東邦神姫だ！
と～ほ～しんき！
TK... Oh!
と～ほ～しんき！グワッ！
知らねぇよ。
Never heard of 'im.
フフフ…　すげぇな。いいだろう。
相手してやるよ　小僧。→
Wow.
Fine. I'll fight you, punk.
オレに勝ったら人質は放してやる。
If you beat me, I'll release the hostages.
You sure you want to give up
your hostages that easily?
いいのかよ。せっかくの人質を
そんな簡単に放して。
It's fine. Their purpose was
only to call you out here.
いいんだよ。そいつらは　てめぇを
ここに呼び出す為だけの→
コマだ。それ以上の
価値なんてねぇんだよ。
They have no other value to me.
フフッ　頭にきたか？→
Angry? Then, come at me!
そら　こいよ。
ここだよ　ここ。
Here! Hit me right here!
（ゴキン！）
Bingo!
《ビンゴ！てめぇが殴ったのは
オレの腹をおおった→
What you just hit was an 8mm
ceramic plate over my stomach!
厚さ８ミリのセラミック板だ！》
Now there's no way you'll
be able to use that fist...
《これでもう　お前の拳は
使いものに…》
うっ…ぐあっ！
（不良達）ああ…。
ああ…。
がはっ…。
立てよ。
Stand up.
You had something on your
stomach, didn't you?
腹に何か仕込んでんだろ？
《ゼブルスペルが鳴動している》
The Zebul Spell is reacting...
いいねぇ…フフフ…！
Nice...
最高だよ　お前！
You're awesome!
《はっ　バカが！
受け止めやがった！→
Fool! You tried to stop it!
That's my special 1.2 million volt stun-gun!
特注１２０万ボルトの
スタンバトンだ！》
Himekawa-san's broken out his Devil's Shock!
出た！
姫川さんのデビルズショック！
He'll be out like a light for half a day!
半日は意識が吹っ飛ぶぜ！
フフフ…。
Baby Beel's crying hurts way more.
ベル坊の夜泣きの方が全然いてぇ。
What?!
何っ！？げえぇ～！
You've got to be kidding me!
うっそだろ！？
お前ら　人質を使え！
Guys, use the hostages!
おお～っ！
Okay! Don't move!
よ～し　動くな。
それ以上動いたら→
If you move, then your wife is...
てめぇの嫁が…あ？
（ドガガガ！）
あああ…。
I know what you are capable of now.
貴様の器は知れた。消えろ！
Begone.
ほおおぉ…。
Baby Beel...
ベル坊。
ダァ！
A man must follow through on
something once he decides it.
男は一度決めたことは
貫き通さなきゃならねえ。
I said that, right?
そう言ったよな？
ダァ！
Yeah...
でもなぁ　ダチがやられて
黙ってるのは…→
But watching your friends get done in without
doing something? That's not being a man at all!
男ですらねぇ！
Got it?
わかるな？
ダ！
ヒッ！ま　待て！
W-Wait...
ウウウ…！
うわあぁ…うわぁ！
Zebul Blast!
ゼブルブラストォー！！
（爆発音）
あ…あ…あああ…ウッ！
ああ？
I cannot believe it... He drew out enough
power to have killed a normal man.
《信じられん。常人なら
死んでもおかしくないほどの→
魔力を注ぎこまれたはず。
なのに…》
And yet...
アイ～。
なんだよ？
What?
フン！行くぞ。
Let's go.
'kay!
はぁ～い。
待て！コラ！
Hold it, you!
Don't you have something to say?
てめえ　言う事があんだろ！
It's not me... You made Baby Beel worried!
オレだけじゃねえ！
ベル坊だって　てめぇを心配して！
フン！坊っちゃまは
私の心配などせん。
The master does not worry for me.
He is just channeling your anger.
貴様の怒りに　あてられただけだ。
あんな事おっしゃって→
You said that, but you're
actually happy, yes?
本当は　うれしいんでしょう？
ん？
Why not simply be happy about the
progress between him and the master?
坊っちゃんと　男鹿殿の成長→
素直に喜んだらどうですか？大したものじゃないですか。
It is quite something, yes?
フン…成長か。
Progress?
確かに　大したものだな。
It is... quite something...
Wow.
ワオ。
I did it again.
またやっちまったな。
（古市）ああ　すまん。
Yeah. Sorry.
Don't apologize now, sheesh. I
won't be able to sound all cool!
あやまんなよ　先に。
ボロカス言えなくなるじゃねえか。
Sorry...
すまん…。
だから　あやまんなっつってんだろ！
ぶっ殺すぞ　コラッ！
I said, don't apologize!
I'll kill you, damn it!
あ？…何じゃこりゃああ！！
What the hell is this?
What, you only noticed now?
ク～ス～…。
（古市）何だ　今頃　気付いたのか？
W-W-What?!
ななな　何だだと～！？
てめぇのせいだろ！
This is your fault! This is all
your fault for gettin' captured!
てめぇが捕まったりするから
オレがこんな目に！
（古市）いてっ！いってぇな！
このヤロ～！
That hurts, damn it!
やるのか！？コラァ！
なんだよ～！
キャ～キャキャキャ…！
Amazing, Oga! You defeated
Himekawa from Ishiyama's TKKH!
Whatever! What'll I do
with this Celeb Pistol?
Uh, Zebul Spell.
Anyway, the master is bored.
Play with him.
On the next Beelzebub:
Toys Have Arrived from the Demon World.
We Played Doctor.
It's a double header.
What kind of toys come from the Demon World?
I have a bad feeling about...